Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1929-1995 and undated
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group B, ca. 1957-1989 and undated
    - Atlantic Monthly Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Author Aid Associates (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Author Speaks (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Authors Guild of the Authors League of America, Inc. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - B C Research (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Ballantine Books (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Barn Gallery (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Baron (Puchard W.) Publishing Company (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Barter Theatre (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Behavioral Research Laboratories (Gordon Lish) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Bernard Geis Assocs. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Bill Cooper Associates (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Blairwood Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Black Warrior Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Blue Buildings (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Blue Ridge Review (Chuck Taormina) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Bobs-Merrill (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Botteghe Oscure Anthology (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Bright Leaf Books (Louis Rubin) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Bucknell Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Bucks County Free Library (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Cabellian (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Calliope (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Carolina Quarterly (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Chapman and Hall (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Chicago Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Coastlines Literary Magazine, Alexandra Garrett, Editor (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - College English Association (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Commission of Arts and Humanities (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Contempora (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Cooper Union (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Coward, Mccann, and Geoghehan (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Cresent Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Crown Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Curtis Brown (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Daves, Joan (agent) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - December (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Delacorte Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Denver Quarterly (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Dial Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Dickenson Publishing Co. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Duell, Sloan, and Pearce (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - E. P. Dutton (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Eastgate Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Education Development Corp. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - English Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Esquire (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Explicator (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Fall River Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Farrar, Straus and Giroux (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Film (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Film Journal (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Fire-Eating (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Florida Quarterly (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Ford Foundation (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Forum (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Frank Cooper Associates Agency (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Friends of the Library Richmond, Virginia (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Gambit Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Gelfman, Samual (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - General Artist Corporation (Sam Gelfman) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Genesis West (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Georgia Commission On the Arts (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Godine (David R.) Pubs. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Goldwyn, Samuel, Jr. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Guggenheim Foundation (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Hampton Roads Magazine (Monty St. Leger Joynes) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Harcourt-Brace (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Hard Scuffle (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Harper and Row (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Harper's Magazine (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Harvest (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Hawthorn Books (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Herb Jaffe Associates (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Historical Book Club of N. C. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Holiday Magazine (Monty St. Leger Joynes) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Holloway House Publishing Co. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Houch Advertising (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Houghton-Mifflin (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - House of Books, Ltd. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Houston--Copy of Article (Garrett discusses Houston's culture) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Image Magazine (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Independent Educational Services (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - International Poetry Forum (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Intro (Walton Beacham) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Islen-Tenney Productions (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Jackpine Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Jeopardy (WWSC-- Robert Huff) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Joyful Alternative (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Kansas Magazine: Kansas State University (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Kansas Quarterly (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Kentucky Arts Commission (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Kentucky Poetry Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Kenyon Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Kidd (Virginia) Literary Agents (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Knopf Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Latitudes (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Library of Congress (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Little Brown and Company (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Longman (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Macmillan (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Maine State Commission on Arts and Humanities (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Maine State Library (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Maine Writers Workshop (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Massachusetts Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - McCall Publishing Co. (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Meredith Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Mid-American Review: Bowling Green State University (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Misc. Congratulations and Thank You letters (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Misc. Correspondance about--Samual Goldwyn's lecture trip (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Misc. Correspondance with Magazines (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Misc. Correspondance with Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Misc. Formal Correspondance with individuals (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Misc. Informal Correspondance with individuals (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Mississippi Authority for Educational Television (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Mississippi Quarterly (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Missouri Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Mlada Tvorba (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Modern Language Assoc. of America (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Moore Publishing Co. (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Morris (William) Agency (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Morrison and Kline Public Relations (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Morrow (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Mother Jones (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Nelson Morris Productions (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - NEMLA (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - National Foundation On Arts and Humanities (Nat. Endowment-Arts) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - National Organization for Women (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Negative Capability (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New American Library (NAL) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New Directions (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New Dramatists Committee (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New England Foundation for Arts (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New England Story (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New Literary History (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New Mexico Humanities Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New River Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New South Co. (Nancy Stone) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New Story (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New York Times (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New Virginia Review (Walton Beacham) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - New World Writing (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Nimrod: University of Tulsa (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Norton (W. W.) and Co. (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Notes on Mississippi Writers (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Ohio Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Old Gaol Museum (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Open Places (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Oxford University Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Pantheon Books (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Papers of John Calhoun (Clyde Wilson) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - PEN (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - People Promotion Public Relations (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Per/Se Inc. (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Periphery (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Phlaum (Geo. A.) Publisher (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Phoenix Book Shop (Robert Wilson) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Ploughshares (Dewitt Henry) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Poetry Center: University of Arizona (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Poetry Society of America (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Poetry Society of Virginia (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Poets and Writers (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Prentice-Hall (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Princeton University (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Program for Poets and Fiction Writers (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Puckerbrush Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Pushcart Press (Bill Henderson) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Putman's (G. P.) Sons (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Quarterly West (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Random House (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Red Clay Reader ( Charleen Whisnant) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Review LaBooche (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Reynolda House (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Richard Marek Publishers (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Richmond Mercury (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Richmond Newsletter, James J. Kilpatrick, Editor (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Rusell and Volkening -- agents (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - St. George's Episcopal Church (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - St. Martin's Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Salem Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Samuel French (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Sandlapper (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Saturday Evening Post (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Saturday Review Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Scholastic (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Scott, Foresman and Co. (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Scribner's (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Sewanee Review (George Core) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Seymour Lawrence (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Shenandoah, James Boatwright, Editor (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Singing Wind Publications (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Solo Press (Glenna Luschei) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - SAMLA (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - South Carolina Arts Commission (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - South Carolina Committee for Humanities (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - South Carolina Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - South Carolina Tricentennial Comm. (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Southern Education Foundation (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Southern Humanities Conference (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Southern Partisan (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Southern Regional Council (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Southern Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - State of Florida (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - State of Maine Writers Conference (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Sterling Lord Agency (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Strong Measures Anthology (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Student (WFU) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Studies in Short Fiction (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Style (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Thomas Nelson and Sons (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University, Princeton Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University of Florida Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University of Kentucky (conference) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University of Missouri Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University of New Mexico Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University of North Carolina Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - University of Texas Press: John Edward Weems (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Wesleyan University Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Woman's Club (Richmond, Va.) (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
    - Writers Guild of America (Box Alpha. Corr. B2)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group C, 1958-1981 and undated
    Contains correspondence from friends and colleagues concerning Garrett's work, publications, and speaking engagements. Arranged alphabetically.
    - A 1964-1981 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - B 1960-1977, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - C 1962-1981 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - G 1941-1980 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - H 1958-1977 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - L 1962-1980 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - M 1964-1979 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - P 1965-1981 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - R 1964-1981 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
    - S 1964-1981 (Box Alpha. Corr. C1)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group D, ca. 1964-1981.
    Letters to Garrett from representatives of English departments, writing programs, and presses of American colleges and universities. Arranged alphabetically by the name of the institution.
    - American Academy of Judicial Education (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - American University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Armstrong State College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Bard College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Bennington College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Boston University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Bowling Green State University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Brown University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Case Western Reserve University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Colby College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - College of William and Mary (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Columbia University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Davidson College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Duke University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Eastern College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Eastern Kentucky University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Eastern Washington State College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Emporia State University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Florida State University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Georgia Institute of Technology (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Gilman School (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Hill School (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Hollins College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Indiana State University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Johnson State College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Kansas State Teachers College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Kent State University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Louisiana State University, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Loyola University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Madison College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Mary Baldwin College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Mary Washington College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Memphis State University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Midwestern University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Mississippi State (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Mount Holyoke College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Northern Kentucky University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Old Dominion University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Princeton University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Queens College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Rice University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Roanoke College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Rollins College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Rutgers University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Salem College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Sarah Lawrence College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Southern Illinois University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - State University College at Potsdam (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - State University of New York (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Texas Christian Academy (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Texas Technical University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Alabama (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Arkansas (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of California - Irvine (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Charleston (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Cincinnati (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Florida (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Georgia (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Houston (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Illinois (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Iowa (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Kansas (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Maryland (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Michigan (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Missouri (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Nebraska (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of North Carolina - Chapel Hill (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of North Carolina - Charlotte (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of North Carolina - Greensboro (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Oklahoma (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Pittsburgh (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of South Carolina (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Southern Mississippi (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Tennessee (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Texas (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Utah (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Virginia (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - University of Wisconsin (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Vermont College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Virginia Military Institute (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Washington University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Wesleyan University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - West Virginia Wesleyan College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Westminster College (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
    - Western Washington University (Box Alpha. Corr. D1)
- Audiovisual Material Series, 1970-1996 and undated
  Audiocassettes of Garrett's classes, readings, speeches, workshops, and lectures (arranged chronologically); audiocassettes of lectures, readings, and presentations by other authors (arranged alphabetically by author's name); and audiocassettes of roundtables and panels (arranged chronologically). Box AV 13 contains additional audiocassettes of lectures, readings, and presentations by other authors (arranged alphabetically by author's name). Box AV 14 contains additional audiocassettes of Garrett's classes, readings, speeches, workshops, and lectures (arranged chronologically). Box AV 15 contains additional audiocassettes of roundtables and panels (arranged chronologically). Series also contains a few 7" reel-to-reel audiotapes, a few photographs and videotapes, and some mini-cassettes (unarranged). Includes tapes of Fred Chappell, Josephine Humphreys, Jack Nicholson, Reynolds Price, and Lee Smith. Use copies of individual tapes must be made as needed before usage by researchers.
  - Garrett's Classes, Readings, Speeches, Workshops, and Lectures
    - Garrett's movie class, 1970, June 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett's movie class, 1970, June 22-23, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at EWSC, 1974, July 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at EWSC, 1975, July 1, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at WWSC, 1977, May, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at WWSC, 1977, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at American University, 1977, June, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Johnson State College, 1977, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Johnson State College, 1977, summer, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Johnson State College, 1977, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Wesleyan, 1978, Aug., (3 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Reynolda House, 1978, Oct. 31, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Hollins College, 1978, Dec., (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of North Carolina-Greensboro, 1978, Dec., (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Johnson State College, 1978, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Minnesota, 1978, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett, 1979, Aug. 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Hollins, 1979, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Temple University, 1980, Feb., (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Pennsylvania, 1980, Feb., (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Kansas State University, 1980, April, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Southwestern University, 1980, April, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Brendan Galvin's class, 1980, June 11, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Virginia, 1981, Feb. 18, (4 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at USC, 1981, Mar. 17, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett: readings, 1981, March, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Bennington College, 1981, June 29, and at University of Southern Maine, 1981, July 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Bennington College, 1981, June 29, and at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, (4 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett: opening remarks, 1981, July 18, and at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, (3 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, and at Johnson State College, 1981, July 27, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, and at Johnson State College, 1981, July 29, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, and at American University, 1981, Sept. 16, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at American University, 1981, Sept. 16, (3 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Clemson and USC, 1981, Nov., (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Vermont College, 1982, Jan. 9, (3 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Charleston, 1982, March 23, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Charleston, 1982, March 30, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Converse College, 1982, April 3, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Converse College, 1982, April 3, and at Johnson State College, 1982, May 5, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Johnson State College, 1982, May 5, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Bennington, 1982, July 5, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast and at Johnson State College, 1982, July, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast, 1982, July, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Northern Kentucky University, 1982, Sept. 13, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett: Virginia Military Institute Panel, 1982, Sept. 30, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Hollins, 1982, Oct. 19, and at Wesleyan, 1982, Oct. 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Wesleyan, 1982, Oct. 21, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Tennessee, 1982, Nov. 3, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at 704 Gallery, Richmond, Va., 1982, Nov. 18, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Washington and Lee, 1982, Dec. 1, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Florida State University, 1983, Jan. 28, (3 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Cooper Union, 1983, Feb. 16, (3 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Charleston, 1983, April 14, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett, 1983, Aug. 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Hardin-Simmons University, 1983, Nov. 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Roger Williams, 1983, Nov. 17, and at YMHA, Philly, 1983, Nov. 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Roger Williams, 1983, fall, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Alabama and at Roger Williams, 1983, Fall, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett: interview, 1983, Nov., (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Penn State, 1984, Feb. 16, and at University of Virginia, 1984, Feb. 20, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Virginia, 1984, Feb. 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett: Film and Social Issues class, 1984, Feb. 28, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Carnegie Mellon and VCU, 1984, March 14-15, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Michigan, 1984, March 20, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at University of Minnesota, 1984, March 22, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett's movie class, 1984, March 26, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at George Mason University, 1984, March, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett at Michigan, 1984, April 2, (2 tapes) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett's movie class, 1984, April 3, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett, 1984, April 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)
    - Garrett with NEH journalists, 1984, April 6, (1 tape) (Box AV 1)